Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
HEROES NEXT DOOR
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
ALL CHARACTERS, PROFESSIONS, PLACES,
COMPANIES, ORGANIZATIONS,
ETHNIC GROUPS AND EVENTS ARE NOT REAL.
ALL CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED
SAFELY UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION.
- Here he comes.
- He's here!
- He's out!
- Please say something!
Please tell us what's going on.
NANO POWER BUTANE GAS
Was it really a butane gas explosion?
Was it really butane gas?
Why the sudden rush
with the investigation?
Please say something!
Please!
If it led to some hair burning
or a dining table blowing up,
then it would've made sense.
NANO POWER BUTANE GAS RESEARCHER
But butane gas blowing up
a whole ATM booth?
You've got to be kidding me.
Why would North Korea even need to bother
experimenting with missiles, then?
They should just use our butane gas!
HARDWARE DREAM TREE STATIONERY
When this blew up,
I was standing right here.
The only reason I survived
was because I ducked so quickly.
If I were even slightly slower,
I could've died.
MAMMOSEU MART DELIVERY MAN
Someone died in the ATM booth overnight,
yet new ATM machines were set up
by the next morning.
Is anyone really that rushed for cash?
Somebody just died.
That's wrong.
Just a few days after the ATM explosion,
another explosion took place in Kiyun-si.
At the bus terminal behind me,
a bus exploded, killing two civilians.
So why hasn't the government
announced anything yet?
BUS DRIVER OF THE EXPLODED BUS
It just exploded.
The bus wasn't even burning
or smoking beforehand.
It just blew up.
MAMMOSEU MART OWNER
It was around 7 a.m.
- It's Mom.
- It's your mom.
- Quiet.
- It's Mom.
She looks nice and scary.
The commander's lead car
was at the bus terminal.
Are you sure you saw it?
And how did you know?
Well, it was a Retona.
Anyway, the traffic was so bad
that my car was barely moving.
But the police and the firefighters
were just standing guard
while soldiers were cleaning up the site.
We send our sons to the military
to protect the nation,
not to clean up some random neighborhood.
If they were there for civilian support,
they should've helped the people.
MAGNIFYING MEDIA
Experts and witnesses
suspect these explosions
to have been bombs instead of butane gas.
The soldiers at the site.
Most importantly, the government seems
too eager to rush to close this case.
The series of explosions in Kiyun-si
is full of questions.
What is true,
and what is the government hiding?
EPISODE 4: WHAT BRINGS YOU TO OUR TOWN?
Did you watch the clip?
Who uploaded that?
You idiot. I told you
to stop these clips from circulating!
Forget it.
Don't let anyone approach Kiyun-si
until we find out what's going on.
It wasn't the 88th Transportation Brigade?
What about the 900th Unit
or the Logistic Support Group?
What do you mean, "standby squad"?
There are witnesses
who saw military vehicles.
And you're seriously saying
no military units were deployed?
Keep searching.
These bastards are messing with me.
Maybe they really don't know
what's going on, either.
That's an even bigger issue.
Look into what those four talked about.
It seems to have something to do
with the explosions in Kiyun-si.
Yes, sir.
- This is just between us.
- Understood, sir.
OPERATION JINDO DOG
TOP SECRET MILITARY SECURITY
CHOI KANG
RECENT MISSION:
HOSTAGE RESCUE IN NORTHERN IRAQ
RESIDENCE: KIYUN-SI, GANGWON-DO
So in summary,
you were checking if he was a spy
or from the National Intelligence Service.
Then you saw those stuffed bunnies
and found this laptop?
Yes.
And the man who died in the ATM explosion
and the man from the building are a team.
And you're saying
the bus terminal explosion is related too?
Yes, this is the stuffed bunny.
That was a great summary.
No wonder you're a journalist.
But how did you take down
that armed agent?
Well...
I can throw some spicy punches!
SPECIAL MARTIAL ARTS
I also served in the HID.
You know that unit, right?
You know, from that movie.
"I'll rip out your gold teeth
and tear you apart."
And I can run really fast.
So we fought that guy
while he ran off.
That's right!
So why are you telling me all this?
I want to uncover the truth
behind Myeong-o's death.
People in our neighborhood are dying.
We need to do something.
Same here.
I wonder if I caused all this trouble
by stealing this laptop.
Hey, how is that your fault?
THEY'RE LISTENING, SHUSH
But the power is off--
It's off, though.
THAT LAPTOP CAN STILL LISTEN IN
EVEN WHEN IT'S OFF
IF THEY CAN TAP US,
THEY CAN TRACK OUR LOCATION
WHAT IF WE USE IT AGAINST THEM?
We need to clone the original laptop!
- We pull the data with forensics...
- And secure evidence!
And since they can track our location
using the laptop...
- We'll purposely expose our location...
- To catch the culprit!
Then we need to start
with the CMOS battery first!
Hey, I can take care of that!
Okay, that's all for today! Dismissed!
Hold up! What are you going to do?
Go to work! I have a job!
Okay, dismissed!
My goodness, that's intense.
That's his car.
- Amazing.
- Will you look at that?
Your car is incredible!
That's neat.
Can I get a ride?
Why are they all coming out of there?
Without me?
INTERNET SECURITY TECHNOLOGY
COMPUTER FORENSIC ANALYSIS
It's going to take forever
on this computer.
Since chip bags are made of
polypropylene and aluminum,
they can block out electric signals,
magnetic field signals,
and even telecommunication signals.
See how dangerous the packaging is?
This is why moms don't let kids eat chips.
Chips are delicious, but dangerous.
- That has nothing to do--
- Of course not.
It's just a joke.
- Officer Park! Someone is dying!
- What?
- Someone's dying!
- Where?
Me.
I'm so low on sugar
that I feel like dying.
Man, you scared me!
Buy me a cup of coffee.
There are cafes all around,
yet you come to the police station?
Hey, you can't get
vending machine coffee at cafes.
I love these.
By the way,
you know the foreigner
who lived in the apartment?
I took something from Unit 203
of that building.
It looks sketchy and dangerous,
so I'd like to leave it with the police.
Why would you take anything?
I didn't know it'd be so dangerous.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm turning myself in, okay?
Cut me some slack.
MAGNIFYING MEDIA
I think we need to take it to a shop.
I could do it, but I don't have the tools.
How much would it be?
For data extraction, memory analysis,
and reverse engineering, it'll be--
So, how much will it be in total?
About 20,000,000 won?
Did you say 2,000 won?
- You don't mean 20,000,000 won, right?
- What?
For this?
Yes.
Man, that's too expensive.
If the five of us were to split it...
No, leave the college student out.
So, 5,000,000 won per person?
We can pay in installments.
Yes, over 120 months.
- Yes, do that.
- We should look for some other ways.
I got it.
- You did?
- What?
With what money? You're a student.
What's the installment plan?
I paid for everything at once.
With my mom's card.
- No way!
- You're rich!
Don't you need to ask your mom first?
Is your mom okay with it?
- No way.
- Man...
Now that we've got the tools,
I'll keep researching until they arrive.
- I'll prepare the follow-up article.
- Okay.
The computer signal disconnected
at the police station,
so these guys will go there.
Let's hide out at the station, then.
You can join us at night after work.
I can't do tomorrow.
I have a housewarming party.
Really?
Who will guard the station
if we're all there?
All where?
Your housewarming party.
Aren't we all invited?
I'm fine.
I should attend as Do-yeon's master.
Have you all lost your minds?
I invited my colleagues from work!
I wasn't going to go, anyway.
My gosh!
Why did you even mention the party, then?
So, you only like your colleagues
and not your neighbors?
Who's going to hide out, then?
We can install a camera
at the station and record it.
The data fee will be so high
without the wi-fi feature
on the memory card, though.
What? How much is that?
I ordered the memory card
with the highest capacity.
My gosh, what are you doing?
We can't have you here
if you do that again!
Hey, boss! You can be my boss now.
- Yes.
- He's the boss.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, thank you.
What the hell?
You scared me to death!
Is that a security camera in your car?
What?
Oh, this? It's a custom-made dash cam.
The data is sent to the cloud memory.
If someone leaves a dent in my car,
this will immediately send me a text.
Text, my ass.
Yong-hui's phone is off,
and look at what you're doing here.
You don't think I know?
Are you guys
making a crew without me?
Because I'm too old?
Did you drink whiskey without me?
Come on. What fun is drinking without you?
You and I are only a year apart, too.
I'm just as old as you are.
Have fun with your security camera.
Huh?
Bye, Su-il.
I'll call you later.
Don't get sulky, okay?
What do we need?
Soju and beer, four bottles each.
- Four bottles of soju!
- And beer.
One bottle, two...
Ssamjang.
Ssamjang!
I need a large batch of short rib cuts.
Short rib cuts?
- Would two of these be good?
- Yes.
I'd also like two packs of pork belly.
Pork belly?
Where's Dad?
- Did we get everything?
- Yeah.
- Let's go now.
- Okay.
All right.
- Here you go.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
- Goodbye!
- Have a good party.
- Goodbye, cutie!
- Bye!
- Hi, Su-il.
- See you around.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi, Do-yeon. Have a good day.
You seem awfully sulky again.
Here. For the gas station
at the intersection.
They don't even have customers
because they don't take card payments.
So why are they always ordering
so much coffee?
Why do you care
if they chug liters of coffee every day?
You're too strict on me!
You make me feel terrible
for just getting a drink with the guys.
Now, Yong-hui and Byeong-nam
are having fun without me.
Are they leaving you out?
Of course not.
It's all because
you're as scary as a tiger.
Everyone's too scared to say anything.
I married a tiger!
Where are you going? Come here.
Roar!
Let's go!
- Left, right, down, up!
- Right on!
Special combat martial arts!
Oh, wow!
The best!
Do-yeon, you're so good. You're the best.
Is that all?
No, come here.
Uncle will give you some money.
Do-yeon, put your hands together.
Fine, I'll give you two bills.
Thank you.
Do-yeon,
what's your favorite thing in the world?
Going to the amusement park with Daddy.
But Daddy is always too busy.
I also want to go,
but that man won't let me.
Do-yeon, beg this uncle
to give Daddy a day off.
Please let my Dad
take me to the amusement park.
Do-yeon, don't put Uncle in a pickle.
She really loves amusement parks.
No pressure, sir.
Just give in. She wants to go.
No pressure.
Fine, take a day off
and go to the amusement park with her.
You don't need to do that.
Yes!
Honey, go to the convenience store
and get some beer.
Okay.
How refreshing.
The Vice Minister seems to be
looking into who was at the site.
What the hell is his deal?
- We don't know who's behind it yet?
- No.
You know how
the first victim was a foreigner?
There was something about
"a new day" or whatever online.
Felt like it could be a cult.
Why don't we just go with that
and blame a cult?
You think I haven't thought of that?
That's the easiest way.
But those bombs keep going off,
only in Kiyun-si.
That Eun-jae keeps asking...
Oh, gosh! See?
NA EUN-JAE
Speak of the devil.
Ridiculous.
She's just scared the plans
for the specialized zone will be canceled.
That specialized zone plan
is what led us to this.
Anyway,
if they find out
it was our bombs exploding in Kiyun-si,
it's over for all of us.
Stay on your toes.
Yes, sir.
The call cannot be completed.
Please leave a voice message...
Why, that little...
Pick up your damn phone!
Drop me off up there.
Yes, ma'am.
MAMMOSEU MART
Welcome...
Hey.
That's not a way to greet your customer.
You're not a customer
if you don't buy anything.
How much is this?
Keep the change.
Let me ask you something.
You've only visited
during election periods
since graduating from high school.
What brings you here?
You know how busy I am.
Since you're one of the leaders,
you hear everything
in this neighborhood, right?
Did anyone record a video
of the ATM booth explosion?
What if they did?
What are you trying to pull now?
Pull what? You're unbelievable.
I'm a congresswoman of our nation.
You saw me install
those smart security cameras
for this town's safety.
What are the ladies of the town saying?
They won't vote for you in the next term
because you took too long.
Eun-jae,
people don't like to go near you, do they?
- What?
- You can take this.
Chew it up.
Sure, I'll chew the damn thing.
- Here it comes.
- It's here.
- Gosh.
- Over here!
It's too early.
- Come on!
- Don't say that!
Thank you for coming, sir.
Move more often
so we can enjoy your wife's cooking again.
What are you saying? Just get in.
- Bye.
- Round Two?
- Come on!
- Go home!
- Get home safely.
- Goodnight!
- You can go, too.
- Let's go.
- Thanks for the feast.
- Let's grab a drink.
- My goodness!
- Come on, then.
- Let's have another round.
- Go home.
No, I'm fine.
- No!
- Please!
Let's grab another drink.
Use the company card.
Gosh, I'm tired.
Who are you?
You up?
Place your hands on the wheel, palms down.
Okay.
I had to wait
because I couldn't unlock your phone.
There we go.
If this falls off, you're dead.
I'm not kidding.
What?
It's me.
Is he with you?
Yes, but...
He got me.
Choi Kang?
Don't be stupid.
Just take the package I sent.
The glove compartment.
Take the phone and let the man go.
Are you the one who pulled off
that "new day" bullshit?
Who are you?
How did you know I lived here?
Why isn't he answering?
It got disconnected.
What?
I told you you'd die if this fell off.
But you took it.
HARDWARE DREAM TREE STATIONERY
Should I say I received or stole it?
It either looks like a burner phone
or an encrypted one.
It's an encrypted phone.
- How do you know?
- I can tell by looking at it.
Good for you, JDD.
Aren't these only used in the military?
He knows my name and where I live.
Could it be those guys?
Are they trying to contact you with this
because we blocked the satellite signals?
He didn't seem to be on the same side
as the satellite laptop guys.
Not those guys?
The military?
Not sure.
How's Mr. Lee doing with the laptop?
He's having a blast.
Money really is good, huh?
Okay.
VEOTIGO INSURANCE
Your subordinates
are working hard outside,
and here you are,
sitting cozy in the office.
Are you picking a fight?
You want a piece of this?
No, I feel bad for you,
working at the office all by yourself.
You didn't let me finish.
Why are you so irritated? Menopause?
I should have just ignored you.
I know! You've worked with me
for long enough.
There's no need to respond to everything.
I sent the insurance payout
for Ms. Lee Seo-hui today.
Really?
Thank you, sir!
Did you receive
the insurance payout, Ms. Lee?
I'm glad it all worked out.
Did you also receive compensation
for the house damage?
I see.
No, they'll send the money soon.
Okay.
Please take care of yourself.
Okay, bye.
GODFATHER
LOANS WITHOUT COLLATERAL OR GUARANTEE
LOAN AVAILABLE IMMEDIATELY
Shoulder...
INSURANCE BASTARD
This little shit.
It's him again. Seriously...
I'll take the call.
Sure.
What?
Hey, Godfather.
You can't be a loanshark
and not pay on time.
Who do you think you're calling?
Aren't you the guy who smashed the table?
Was your name Sang-ho? Seong-ho?
You want me to cut your stomach open?
You think our boss is your buddy?
Oh, you're his little brother.
I didn't know it was a family business.
Tell your big brother
that his payment is overdue.
Where are you?
In your heart.
Hello?
The bastard just hung up
after saying whatever he wanted.
He's crazy.
Hey, dipshit,
are you asking me to kill you?
I mean, who actually wants to die?
And you'll need to find me first
if you want to kill me.
You brave little shit,
you don't think I can find you?
No.
Hello?
Would you look at this bastard?
What now?
Hello, Mr. Choi.
The father of Choi Do-yeon
from Kiyun Dream Kindergarten.
Or shall I call you
Ms. Hwang Mi-gyeong's husband?
Where are you?
I'm a master at finding people,
you piece of shit.
So, where are you?
You're scared, aren't you?
Our address is on our business card.
You moron! Why would you tell him that?
GODFATHER
LOANS WITHOUT COLLATERAL OR GUARANTEE
FIVE-MINUTE LOAN
WITHOUT COLLATERAL OR GUARANTEE
He's actually here.
You're really here.
Just don't kill them.
Don't kill them.
What are you blabbering to yourself?
All right, I'll save one limb each
for every question you answer.
Or I'll break as many limbs
as the number of questions I ask.
Hey, you high or something?
One.
How did you find out
the names of my family?
From your mom. Got a problem?
It's a business secret.
Two.
Did you ever get near the kindergarten?
What if we did?
Don't answer him. Just beat him up.
Stop him!
Damn it!
No killing.
Shit!
I did it!
Stop!
Please stop!
Stop it, okay?
Come here.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault, okay?
You were behind it, weren't you?
I'm sorry!
I swear, I'll stay out of your hair.
I won't ever bother you again.
No, wrong answer.
Please...
You can't open it without a key...
What now?
Forensic analysis is done!
Everyone, to the ardware store.
No, hardware.
HARDWARE DREAM TREE STATIONERY
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hello.
There they go again.
They've left me out again. Just me.
I recovered the map
and the dashcam footage.
Good work. You're amazing.
The tools really helped.
That was totally worth the money.
Hey, give me some credit, too.
I built this radio-wave-blocking tent
by hand.
It was supposed only to block radio waves,
but it almost blocked my life out, too!
I nearly died from the heat.
Still got the job done, though.
That's true.
It costs about 30,000,000 won
to build the real thing.
But I didn't even use
one-hundredth of that.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
I'll check the footage
and upload it right away.
- Okay.
- All right.
Mr. Lee, could I have a copy
of the dashcam footage?
Here you go.
And just call me Yong-hui.
Is that all right, Yong-hui?
Yes!
Anyway, great work.
Did you end up arguing with Byeong-nam?
No, why would I argue with him?
That's a waste of time.
You did, huh?
Honey, the thing is,
I just saw Min-seo's tutor,
Producer Kim of Magnifying Media, and Kang
all gathering at the hardware store.
Without me.
So? Join them.
Me? I can't.
How could I go when I wasn't invited?
How could I join them? I can't.
Even Chun-bae hasn't seen Byeong-nam
since Myeong-o's funeral.
The Byeong-nam we knew of is gone.
He's changed.
And I'm alone.
It's fine.
I'll just clean that up.
Who am I to be sad?
What are they scheming?
- Good work.
- Yong-hui, you're awesome.
It's nothing.
- Good work.
- It was impressive.
Oh, hello.
I'll get going first.
I have some editing to do.
Please excuse me.
I'd better get going, too.
Me too.
Hello, ma'am.
I need a shower.
Bye.
I also need to tidy up the stationery...
Byeong-nam.
What now?
What are you guys plotting?
HARDWARE DREAM TREE STATIONERY
She's been in there for over 20 minutes.
What's taking her so long?
Man...
It must be really tough
for my poor Byeong-nam.
It's okay. I live with that every day.
It was just too odd, okay?
Explosions kept going off
in the neighborhood.
Kang and I just so happened
to witness one of them,
so we teamed up
to get to the bottom of it.
That's all.
You traitor.
So you're family
only when you're out drinking at night?
All these things are happening,
and you guys are keeping it from us?
What's the point of scaring everyone
with all of this?
Am I telling you to tell everyone in town?
You should've at least told
Chun-bae and me!
We're also leaders of the neighborhood.
Chun-bae is too busy
with his wife right now,
and you're...
What?
My naive little husband
thought you were pretending to be busy
to hang out with Yong-hui
and Kang without him.
He's pouting like crazy.
That's not all.
He thinks you guys don't come to the store
because you're scared of me.
That's not entirely wrong.
Damn it.
Come on!
If Su-il knew about this,
he would've told the whole town!
He's friendly, yes.
But he can keep a secret better than you.
I don't care
about what you guys are doing.
Just don't leave my husband out. Got that?
Get to the bottom of it...
What can you even do?
Honey, my boss gave me a day off
to go to the amusement park.
Really? That's great.
Do-yeon will be so happy.
But do we have to go?
With all that news
about park rides malfunctioning.
How do you give her baths?
Aren't you scared she'll drown, too?
You're so overprotective of her.
All of Do-yeon's friends
have been to amusement parks.
All except Do-yeon.
Still, we don't need to go now--
We do. You got a day off.
Cut the crap. We're taking her.
- Lights out.
- Yes, ma'am.
The video will be up at midnight.
Please like, comment, and subscribe.
Here's the dashcam footage
we were able to track down.
On the laptop of the foreigner
who died in the ATM explosion
was a video of the crash
at the Kiyun Intersection,
along with a suspicious map.
What's scarier is that there was a message
foreshadowing a terrorist attack.
Despite the government's announcement
that the three explosions were accidental,
we've found evidence
that these explosions were planned.
In the next video,
we'll reveal the organizations and people
associated with the explosions,
based on our research.
Thank you.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO OUR CITY?
A NEW DAY IS COMING
Welcome!
It'd be good to avoid crowds
as much as we can.
Whatever.
You sound like an old man.
Just let Do-yeon have a blast, okay?
It's been her dream
to come here with her dad.
She's living her dream today.
Oh, a bunny!
Daddy, come on!
- Don't run, Do-yeon! You'll trip!
- She'll be fine.
She's very athletic
because she takes after me.
I hope she takes after me
for everything else.
Daddy is coming to get you!
How cute. My eldest son
is playing with my daughter.
I'm coming, too!
Here she comes!
Do-yeon!
#KIYUN-SI, #BOMBING,
#TERRORIST THREAT, #A NEW DAY IS COMING
NATIONAL THREAT RESPONSE CENTER
Yes, this is the situation room.
A bomb threat in Kiyun-si?
- So you're saying that...
- This is the situation room.
What? A bomb threat?
On social media?
Attention, everyone!
Get all security camera footage
from Kiyun-si on the screen
and look for any odd signs.
KIYUN MIDDLE SCHOOL
What do you want to do tomorrow?
Eat something good?
Sure.
- Bye!
Sir, look at this!
What is it?
Look over here.
You have tutoring today, right?
Don't be late.
Yeah, I'm waiting for the bus now.
Did you go over the material?
Come on, stop nagging me.
Whose bag is that?
I should put it on the bench.
MAMMOSEU MART
Min-seo!
You can't come in, it's dangerous.
Stay back.
- Let me through.
- It's dangerous. Please step back.
- Please step back.
Let me through!
Chief?
Let me through. I'm going in.
No, the EOD team is on the way.
What's going on?
It's my daughter in there.
No, please!
Min-seo!
Mom...
Min-seo,
it'll be over in no time.
You trust me, right?
Yes.
Good girl.
It's okay.
It'll be fine. Slowly.
I got you.
Let me take a look.
Min-seo.
Look at me.
We have more than enough time.
Min-seo, I can do it, okay?
It'll be okay.
It's all over.
It's all good now.
Good job, Min-seo.
It's all over.
Min-seo. I'm here, sweetie.
I'm so proud of you.
Good job, Min-seo.
You were amazing.
This afternoon, a suspicious backpack
possibly containing a bomb was reported.
The police and military
responded immediately.
The bomb in question
was revealed to be a fake,
with no explosive risk.
The conspiracies and fake news
are getting out of control.
Look at it now.
Even kids are pulling terrorist pranks.
Hey!
Are you fucking kidding me?
They're all anti-state forces!
Arrest them right now
and interrogate them.
MAGNIFYING MEDIA
What? What the hell?
Hey! What's going on?
Hold on!
Hey, don't touch the server!
What's going on?
Who the hell are you?
Hey, where...
Where are you taking me?
What is this?
Damn it!
I want ice cream.
You had some earlier.
Can I have one more?
No, too much cold food
will upset your stomach.
My stomach is fine.
I want another one, too.
Mommy, just one more, please?
I promise not to upset my stomach.
She says she won't upset her stomach.
- Mom.
Stop it.
It's on you if Do-yeon gets a stomachache.
Yes! I'll take care of you
if you get a stomachache!
Okay!
The line for ice cream is long,
so I'll get it for us.
Okay, I'll go to the bathroom
with Do-yeon.
- Okay, I'll meet you there.
- Okay.
I want strawberry ice cream!
Okay, strawberry it is!
All right.
Do-yeon, I also need to use the bathroom.
- So don't go anywhere and wait, okay?
- Okay.
Here.
Hi, could we use the sink?
Do-yeon! Where did you get that ice cream?
He said it was from you.
Who?
Some guy.
It's fine. You can eat it. It's melting.
HEROES NEXT DOOR
- Good shot!
- Did it swerve? Where did it go?
- It went straight.
- As straight as an arrow.
- As long as I made it.
Hey.
Yes, Kim Seok-jun speaking.
Come on.
If you start complicating things,
it won't end, you know?
Imagine what a mess it'll be
if we let anti-state forces run wild.
Terrorism isn't just about bombs.
Spreading false news to our people
is also terrorism.
I'll take care of it, all right?
I'll send in someone good.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, exactly.
Let's grab a meal sometime. Okay.
Bye.
This thick-headed moron.
- Let's get moving.
- Okay.
Why can't he just take a hint?
Who's this?
Hello?
Minister Kim.
Yes, who's this?
It's me,
Sullivan.
James Sullivan?
The government could be controlling it,
or they could really be moving in secret.
Who are these bastards
playing with bombs in our neighborhood?
She was the youngest drill instructor
of the 707th Unit?
What's with all the special forces
in this neighborhood?
What happened?
- Minister Kim, you could get screwed.
- Screw you.
Something's going on,
and Kiyun-si is at the center of it.
They would have been smart.
Then shouldn't we
find a way to outsmart them?
Subtitle translation by Min-sun Kim